So, you hate cleaning your room. Listen,
it's not a crime. Um I literally loathe
to clean my room, or I used to.
Or I still do, if I'm being honest. And
I tell myself that I don't mind when
it's messy, because I have a really
large capacity to ignore mess. It's like
I don't even see it. But I know this is
only half true, because even though I
don't consciously see it, I notice that
when my space is clean, I feel so much
more peace. And it's like my brain is
using so much CPU to actively ignore the
messiness of the space. Anyway, I'm not
saying this will work for you. This is
just what works for me. Instead of
telling myself that I'm cleaning my
room, I like to tell myself that I'm
beautifying my space. And I like this
because cleaning to me feels
subtractive. It's about taking things
away, and that doesn't feel creative to
me, though it may be. I like the idea of
beautifying, and the idea that instead
of subtracting, I am creating space. And
space is a thing that I can make. I can
make beauty with my two hands. And it
makes me think of my own maintenance
around my brain, or my mind. It's like
when things are cluttered and messy on
the inside, I'm like, "Things are messy.
Things are bad." But it's like, "Okay,
is it bad, or does it just need a little
care, a little tending?" And I like to
think of myself as like it is my sacred
duty to take care of my space, and to
take care of my mind. And when I put in
the effort, I get to see that maybe it
was beautiful all along.
My space and my mind, it just needed a
little love. Anyway,
here's a song about that.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Clean I clean stone and surface. I make
it beautiful [music] with my hands. I
unearth it. Little love for things that
I [singing] adore.
Look how [music] beautiful [singing] you
can see it when I put in the effort. I
learn [singing and music] to reveal it.
Beauty in my mind [music] and in my
room. [singing]
When I let the old pass through.
I make space to feel something [music]
beautiful.
And
new.
>> [music]
>> New.
[singing]
[music]
>> Look at how I make things with my hands.
The hardest part of all of it
is starting once again. [music]
Look at what becomes
when I create.
>> [music]
>> Look at how I grow when I have space.
Clean up [singing and music] every stone
and surface. I make it beautiful with my
hands. I unearth it.
>> [music]
>> Little love for the things that I adore.
>> Look how beautiful you can see it when I
put in the [singing and music] effort. I
learn to reveal it. Beauty in my
[singing] mind and in my room.
When I let the old
pass through.
I make space to feel something [music]
beautiful.
And new.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I made it.
>> [music]
I made it.
I make [singing and music] it.
New. [snorts]
>> [music]
>> That's my song.
Uh it's out now. Everywhere you find
music. My name is Tessa Violet. That
song is called The Clean Up Song or
something different if I decide to
change the name of that song before I
put this out. I'm putting out a song
every month this year. So if you want to
be notified when I put out the next
song, there's a link in the bio. And um
or you can see all the songs that are
already out. And if you really want to
be a friend, you can support me on
Patreon.
>> [laughter]
>> Anyway, I hope you're having an amazing
day. And I hope that um getting to clean
your room can be a like spiritual
experience for you. You're not just
cleaning. You are creating beauty in
your space and in your mind.
Okay.
Bye.
I got to go.
>> Mhm.